A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - M (Box 606, Folder 1-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - N-O (Box 607, Folder 1-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - P-S (Box 608, Folder 1-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - S-T (Box 609, Folder 1-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - U-University of, A-C (Box 610, Folder 1-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - University of, D-N (Box 611, Folder 1-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - University of, N-Z (Box 612, Folder 1-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - U-V (Box 612, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - W-Z (Box 613, Folder 1-2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Air Force Academy Foundation (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Air University, 1960-1965 (Box 613, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1973 (Box 614, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - American School of Classical Studies in Athens, 1963-1974 (Box 614, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - American University in Beirut, 1971-1976 (Box 614, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - American University in Cairo, 1973-1976 (Box 614, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Antioch College, 1967-1971 (Box 614, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Bard College, 1967-1971 (Box 614, Folder 6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Bennington College, 1967-1972 (Box 614, Folder 7)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Boston University, 1965-1966 (Box 614, Folder 8)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Bowdoin College, 1971 (Box 615, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Bradford Junior College, 1965-1971 (Box 615, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Bradford Junior College - Printed Material, 1965-1968 (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Brandeis University, 1962-1966 (Box 615, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Briarcliff College, 1962-1966 (Box 615, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Brown University - Contributions, 1963-1966 (Box 615, Folder 6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Brown University, 1962-1970 (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Brown University - Printed Material, 1962-1966 (Box 616, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Bryn Mawr, 1966-1971 (Box 616, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - California Institute of Technology, 1962-1973 (Box 616, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Cambridge University, 1970-1973 (Box 616, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Case Institute of Technology, 1962-1966 (Box 616, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Catholic University of Puerto Rico, 1966-1969 (Box 616, Folder 6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - City University of New York, 1967-1976 (Box 616, Folder 7)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Clark University, 1967-1971 (Box 617, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Colby College, 1962-1964 (Box 617, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Colgate University, 1963-1966 (Box 617, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Colgate University - Festival of the Creative Arts, 1963-1964 (Box 617, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Colgate University - Fortnight of Active Arts, 1967-1968 (Box 617, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - College of Human Services, 1970 (Box 617, Folder 6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - College of Idaho, 1967-1970 (Box 617, Folder 7)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - College of the Potomac, 1968-1969 (Box 617, Folder 8)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - College of the Atlantic - Printed Material, 1972-1976 (Box 618, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - College of the Virgin Islands, 1962-1976 (Box 618, Folder 2-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - College of the Virgin Islands - A-Z, 1967-1976 (Box 619, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - College of the Virgin Islands - Amalgamation Study, 1963-1972 (Box 619, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - College of the Virgin Islands - Printed Material (Box 620, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - College of William and Mary, 1962-1966 (Box 620, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - A-C, 1961-1976 (Box 620, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - Academy of Political Science (APS) (Box 620, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - D-Z (Box 621, Folder 1-2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - American Assembly, 1962-1972 (Box 621, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - Asian Center - Kent Hall, 1963-1966 (Box 621, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - Columbia College Citizenship Council, 1963-1966 (Box 621, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - Graduate School of Journalism, 1961-1971 (Box 621, Folder 6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - Contributions, 1961-1966 (Box 622, Folder 1-2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - Oral History, 1962-1975 (Box 622, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - Oral History - JDR 3rd (Box 622, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Columbia University - School of International Affairs, 1963 (Box 622, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Connecticut College, 1962-1971 (Box 623, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Cooper Union, 1962-1965 (Box 623, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Cornell - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 623, Folder 3-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Cornell - Contributions, 1963-1966 (Box 623, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Cornell - Cornell Plantations, 1967-1976 (Box 623, Folder 6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Cornell - Office of Regional Resources and Development, 1964-1971 (Box 623, Folder 7, Box 624, Folder 1-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Cornell - School of Hotel Administration - Dorado Beach Scholarships, 1962-1971 (Box 625, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Dag Hammarskjold College, 1969-1971 (Box 625, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Dartmouth College - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 625, Folder 3-5, Box 626, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Dartmouth College - Alumni - Printed Matter, 1972-1977 (Box 626, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Dartmouth College - Grenville Clark Fund, 1972-1976 (Box 626, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Dartmouth College - Phi Beta Kappa Association of New York, 1972-1976 (Box 626, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Dartmouth College - Psi Upsilon Foundation, 1973-1976 (Box 626, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Dartmouth College - Printed Matter (Box 627, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Educational Policy Center Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 627, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Eisenhower College, 1964-1976 (Box 627, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - EWHA Women's University, Inc., 1967-1971 (Box 627, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Fordham University, 1963-1966 (Box 627, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Franklin and Marshall College, 1964-1965 (Box 628, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - General Beadle State College, 1967-1969 (Box 628, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - George Washington University, 1964-1966 (Box 628, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - George Washington University - School of Medicine, 1964-1966 (Box 628, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Hampshire College, 1969-1970 (Box 628, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - A-Z, 1962-1975 (Box 629, Folder 1-3, Box 630)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Board of Overseers, 1961-1966 (Box 630, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Board of Overseers - Honorary Degrees (Box 631, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Board of Overseers - Presidency (Box 631, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Board of Directors - A-Z (Box 631, Folder 3-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Committee to Visit the Department of Economics, 1962-1970 (Box 631, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Department of Economics (Box 632, Folder 1-2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Contributions - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 632, Folder 3, Box 633, Folder 1-4, Box 634)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Contributions - "The Harvard Independent", 1969-1975 (Box 634, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Department of Economics - Harvard Economics Meeting at University Club, 1967 February 8 (Box 634, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - East Asian Studies, 1973-1976 (Box 635, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - East Asian Studies - Dinner, 1974 May 30 (Box 635, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1961-1976 (Box 635, Folder 3-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Graduate School of Business Administration - Fellowships for Women - Contributions, 1963-1973 (Box 635, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Graduate School of Business Administration - William Barclay Harding Memorial Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 636, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Graduate School of Business Administration - Fellowships for Women, 1966-1976 (Box 636, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Graduate School of Design, 1962-1966 (Box 636, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Graduate School of Education, 1968-1970 (Box 636, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard College Fund, 1962-1976 (Box 637, Folder 1-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School, 1962-1976 (Box 637, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School - Printed Material, 1972-1976 (Box 638, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Memorial Hall, 1967-1974 (Box 638, Folder 2-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Graduate Society for Advanced Study and Research (Box 638, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Graduate Society for Advanced Study and Research - Printed Material, 1961-1976 (Box 639, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Graduate Society for Advanced Study and Research - Rockefeller, David, 1961-1976 (Box 639, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Law School, 1962-1972 (Box 639, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Law School - Printed Material, 1970-1973 (Box 640, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Law School - Rockefeller Family, 1972-1975 (Box 640, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Medical School, 1962-1976 (Box 640, Folder 3-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard-Radcliffe Orchestra, 1965-1967 (Box 641, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard School of Public Health, 1962-1966 (Box 641, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Yenching Institute, 1962-1965 (Box 641, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Yenching Institute - Meetings/Minutes, 1965 (Box 641, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Yenching Institute - Finances, 1965 (Box 641, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Harvard Student Agencies (Box 641, Folder 6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Honorary Degrees, 1967-1971 (Box 642, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Joint Center for Urban Studies at Harvard and M.I.T., 1965-1970 (Box 642, Folder 2-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Peabody Museum, 1975-1976 (Box 642, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Phillips Brooks House Association, 1962-1967 (Box 643, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Phillips Brooks House Association - Contributions, 1968-1971 (Box 643, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Printed Material, 1964-1976 (Box 643, Folder 3-4, Box 644, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Professorship of Canadian Studies, 1960-1971 (Box 644, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Professorship of Canadian Studies - Fund Raising, 1966 (Box 644, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Watts, Alan, 1961-1966 (Box 644, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Harvard University - Michael C. Rockefeller Memorial Fellowship, 1965-1974 (Box 645, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Hebrew Union College - Jewish Institute of Religion, 1963-1971 (Box 645, Folder 2-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Hebrew University, 1965-1966 (Box 645, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Hellenic College, 1967-1969 (Box 646, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Japan International Christian University, 1962-1971 (Box 646, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Johns Hopkins University, 1962-1974 (Box 646, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Keio University, 1962-1964 (Box 646, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Kirksville College of Osteopathy and Surgery, 1963-1965 (Box 646, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Lincoln University, 1964 (Box 646, Folder 6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Long Island University, 1961-1966 (Box 647, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Lynchburg Baptist College, 1974-1975 (Box 647, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Macalester College, 1964-1966 (Box 647, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Manhattan College, 1962-1966 (Box 647, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Marlboro College, 1962-1964 (Box 647, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1962-1976 (Box 648, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - A-R (Box 648, Folder 2-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - S-Z (Box 651, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Abby Rockefeller Mauze Professorship, 1968-1975 (Box 649, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Minutes/Meetings, 1972-1977 (Box 649, Folder 2-4, Box 650, Folder 1-4, Box 651, Folder 1-2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Board of Trustees, 1965-1975 (Box 651, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Center for International Studies, 1962-1966 (Box 652, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Contributions, 1962-1974 (Box 652, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Leadership Campaign (Box 652, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Ottauquechee, 1971-1976 (Box 652, Folder 4-6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Printed Material, 1972-1976 (Box 653, Folder 1-2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Releases, 1969-1976 (Box 653, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Reports, 1970-1976 (Box 653, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Reports of Visiting Committees A-Z, 1971-1976 (Box 654, Folder 1-2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - MIT - Alfred P. Sloan School of Management, 1961-1971 (Box 654, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Meharry Medical College, 1970-1976 (Box 655, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Michigan State University, 1969-1970 (Box 655, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Middlebury College, 1967 (Box 655, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Midpeninsula Free University, 1969 (Box 655, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Morehouse College, 1969-1971 (Box 655, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Morehouse College - Atlanta University Center, 1970-1971 (Box 655, Folder 6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - New School for Social Research (Box 655, Folder 7)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - New York University - A-M (Box 656, Folder 1-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - New York University - N-Z (Box 657, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - New York University - NYU Medical Center, 1965-1976 (Box 657, Folder 2-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - New York University - Printed Material, 1966-1976 (Box 657, Folder 4, Box 658, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - New York University - School of Education - Dept. of Physical Education Health and Recreation, 1959-1964 (Box 658, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Occidental College, 1962-1966 (Box 658, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Oxford University, 1962-1970 (Box 658, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Penn State University (Box 658, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Pratt Institute, 1962-1970 (Box 659, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Prescott College, 1969-1970 (Box 659, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - A-B (Box 659, Folder 3-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - C-P (Box 660, Folder 1-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - P-Z (Box 661, Folder 1-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Admissions, 1969-1972 (Box 661, Folder 4, Box 662, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - A-Z, 1967-1973 (Box 662, Folder 2-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - Committee on the Curriculum, 1966-1974 (Box 663, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - Committee on Finances, 1968-1975 (Box 663, Folder 2-3, Box 664, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - Committee on Grounds and Buildings, 1969-1975 (Box 664, Folder 2-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - Committee on Health and Athletics, 1967-1973 (Box 665, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - Committee on Plans and Resources, 1967-1974 (Box 665, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - Committee on the Structure of the University (Box 665, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - Committees Miscellaneous, 1969-1972 (Box 665, Folder 4, Box 666, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - Minutes/Meetings, 1968-1975 (Box 666, Folder 2-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Board of Trustees - Urban Studies, 1968 (Box 666, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - James H. Case III, 1967-1969 (Box 667, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Contributions, 1967-1969 (Box 667, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Library, 1967-1971 (Box 667, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - John Foster Dulles Library of Diplomatic History, 1962-1970 (Box 667, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Minutes/Meetings - Executive Committee, 1968-1975 (Box 667, Folder 5-6)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - Printed Material, 1968-1972 (Box 668, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - A-Z, 1962-1973 (Box 668, Folder 2-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Board of Trustees - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 669, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Board of Trustees (Box 669, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Board of Trustees - Committee on Curriculum, 1966 (Box 669, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Board of Trustees - Committee on Finances, 1966 (Box 669, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Board of Trustees - Committee on Honorary Degrees, 1961-1966 (Box 669, Folder 5)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Board of Trustees - Committee on Plans and Resources, 1962-1966 (Box 670, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Board of Trustees - Minutes/Meetings (Box 670, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Contributions, 1975-1976 (Box 670, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Contributions - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 670, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Contributions - Annual Giving, 1962-1966 (Box 670, Folder 5, Box 671, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Contributions - Co-Education for Women/Scholarships for Women, 1971-1976 (Box 671, Folder 2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - JDR 3rd - Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs, 1962-1966 (Box 671, Folder 3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - LSR - A-F, 1966-1976 (Box 671, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - LSR - G-Z, 1966-1976 (Box 672, Folder 1)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - LSR - Board of Trustees, 1972-1976 (Box 672, Folder 2-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - LSR - Board of Trustees - A (Box 672, Folder 4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - LSR - Board of Trustees - A-Commission (Box 673, Folder 1-2)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - LSR - Board of Trustees - Committees - A-Z, 1969-1976 (Box 673, Folder 3-4)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - LSR - Board of Trustees - Con-H (Box 674, Folder 1-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - LSR - Board of Trustees - I-Z (Box 675, Folder 1-3)
  - Education - Colleges/Universities - Princeton University - LSR - Board of Trustees - Annual Reports, 1968-1976 (Box 676, Folder 1)